flytonic.com 2015-12-06

# Privacy Policy | Flytonic

Flytonic.com takes the issue of privacy and security seriously. We assure you that all information collected by us is confidential and will not be shared or sold without consent. Personal information such as email addresses, names, and contact information are needed so we can communicate with you and provide you with the services you have requested.

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on our site, subscribe to our newsletter, or purchase one of our themes or products.

When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name or e-mail address and create a password.

## Purchase Information

We do not store any credit card information.  All transactions are made through a third party (PayPal) and are completely secure.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To send periodic emails that offers news, promotional codes, and discounts related to Las Vegas.
  * To update you on your order status or products updates.

The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information

We use cookies to understand and save your preferences for future visits, keep track of advertisements and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site visitors. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## Third party links

Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.

### Your Consent

By using our site, you consent to our web site privacy policy.

### Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or send an email notifying you of any changes.

## Contact

If you need more information please [contact us](http://www.flytonic.com/contact/).
